Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXI. ORGANIZATION
  - Sub-Series 230-436. Organization
    - Air Transport Industry, 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      1959-Dec. 31, 1960.
    - Air Transport Industry, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Air Transport Industry, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      March 1957-Dec. 1957.
    - Air Transport Industry, 1956-1957 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      Aug. 1956-Feb. 1957.
    - Air Transport Industry, 1956 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      Jan. 1956-July 1956.
    - Air Transport Industry, 1955 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - 230-436(a). Air Transport Industry, 1952-1954 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - 230-436(a). Air Transport Industry, 1948-1951 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Air Transport Industry, 1947 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      Jan. 1947-Dec. 1947.
    - 230-436(a). Air Transport Industry, 1946 (Box 104, Folder 4)
      July 1946-Dec. 1946.
    - 230-436(a). Air Transport Industry, 1945-1946 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      Sept. 1945-June 1946.
    - 230-436(a). Air Transport Industry, 1944-1945 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      1944-Aug. 1945.
    - Air Transport Industry-Employment Figures, 1943-1946 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Air Transport Employees, 1942 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Air Transport Industry, 1946-1947 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-437. Organization
    - Greenwich and Johnsonville Railway, 1943 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      1957-July 1958.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1954-1956 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      Aug. 1950-51.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1949-1950 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      Aug. 1949-July 1950.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      1948-July 1949.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1947 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      March 1947-Dec. 1947.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      Aug. 1946-Feb. 1947.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1946 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      March 1946-July 1946.
    - Northwest Airlines, Inc., 1943-1945 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-438. Organization
    - Capital Airlines, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 5)
      Jan. 1, 1961-May 31, 1961.
    - Capital Airlines, 1959-1960 (Box 105, Folder 6)
      Jan. 31, 1959-Dec. 31, 1960.
    - Capital Airlines, 1957-1958 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines (Capital), 1952-1956 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines (Capital), 1947-1951 (Box 105, Folder 9)
      Oct. 1947-Dec. 1951.
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines (Capital), 1947 (Box 105, Folder 10)
      Feb. 16, 1947-Sept. 1947.
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines (Capital), 1946-1947 (Box 105, Folder 11)
      Nov. 1946-Feb. 15, 1947.
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines (Capital), 1946 (Box 105, Folder 12)
      Sept. 1946-Oct. 1946.
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines (Capital), 1945-1946 (Box 105, Folder 13)
      Oct. 1945-Aug. 1946.
    - Pennsylvania-Central Airlines, 1945 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      March 1945-Sept. 1945.
  - Sub-Series 230-439. Organization
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc., 1959 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      Feb. 1, 1959-Dec. 31, 1959.
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc., 1948-1958 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      Oct. 1946-47.
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      1945-Sept. 1946.
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc., 1940-1944 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Eastern Airlines, Inc.-Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-440. Organization
    - Chicago & Calumet River Railroad Company, 1943 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      1943 May 26
    - Pittsburgh, Shawmut & Northern Railroad, 1941-1946 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-441. Organization
    - Butte, Anaconda & Pacific, 1941-1953 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-442. Organization
    - Hawaiian Railroads: Oahu Railway & Land Company, Hawaii Consolidated Railway, Ltd., and Kahylui Railroad Company, 1941-1944 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-443. Organization
    - Cuyahoga Valley Railroad, 1942-1952 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-444. Organization
    - Conemaugh & Black Lick Railroad Company, 1942-1945 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-445. Organization
    - Chicago Car Interchange Bureau, 1942-1944 (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-446. Organization
    - Baltimore & Eastern Railroad, 1942 (Box 106, Folder 14)
      Nov. 1942.
  - Sub-Series 230-447. Organization
    - Trans-World Airlines, Questionnaire on Airline Organization Survey, 1956 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Trans-World Airlines, 1948-1956 (Box 106, Folder 16)
      May 1948-56.
    - Trans-World Airlines, 1948 (Box 106, Folder 17)
      Feb. 1948-April 1948.
    - Trans-World Airlines, 1947-1948 (Box 106, Folder 18)
      April 1947-Jan. 1948.
    - Trans-World Airlines, 1946-1947 (Box 106, Folder 19)
      June 1946-March 1947.
    - Trans-World Airlines (formerly Transcontinental and Western Air, Inc.), 1943-1946 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      1943-May 1946.
  - Sub-Series 230-448. Organization
    - Colonial Airlines, Inc., 1945-1956 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-449. Organization
    - United Air Lines, 1961-1963 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - United Air Lines, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      June 1, 1961-Aug. 15, 1961.
    - United Air Lines, 1960-1961 (Box 107, Folder 5)
      1960-May 31, 1961.
    - United Air Lines-Air Line Organization Survey Questionnaires, 1956 (Box 107, Folder 6)
      April 1956-Oct. 1956.
    - United Air Lines, Inc., 1947-1956 (Box 107, Folder 7)
      June 1947-56.
    - United Air Lines, Inc., 1945-1947 (Box 107, Folder 8)
      1945-May 1947.
  - Sub-Series 230-450. Organization
    - Southern Pacific Company-New York City, 1940-1945 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-451. Organization
    - East St. Louis Junction Railroad, 1945 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-452. Organization
    - Georgia, Southern & Florida, 1945-1946 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-453. Organization
    - Cedar Rapids & Iowa City Railway, 1945-1954 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-454. Organization
    - Montreal Refrigerating & Storage Ltd., 1943 (Box 107, Folder 13)
      Oct. 11, 1943.
  - Sub-Series 230-455. Organization
    - Western Association of Railway Executives and Affiliated Organizations, 1943-1955 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-456. Organization
    - Natchez & Southern, 1944-1949 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-457. Organization
    - Quebec Railway Company, 1944 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-459. Organization
    - High Point, Thomasville & Denton Railroad, 1957 (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - High Point, Thomasville & Denton Railroad, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - High Point, Randleman, Asheboro & Southern Railroad Company-High Point, Thomasville & Denton Railroad Company, 1944 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-460. Organization
    - Leavenworth Depot & Railroad Company, 1944 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-461. Organization
    - Bus & Truck Employees, 1945-1947 (Box 107, Folder 21)
    - Bus & Truck Employees, 1941-1944 (Box 107, Folder 22)
    - Bus & Truck Employees, 1938-1940 (Box 107, Folder 23)
    - 230-461(c). Bus & Truck Employees-Rock Island Motor Transit Company, 1940-1946 (Box 107, Folder 24)
    - 230-461(b). Bus & Truck Employees, Activities-Joe Preston, 1939-1943 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - 230-461(d). Bus & Truck Lines-Burlington Transportation Company, 1940-1945 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Bus & Truck Employees, 1933-1937 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Bus & Truck Employees, 1928-1931 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-462. Organization
    - Red Caps, Pennsylvania Railroad, 1942-1951 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Red Caps, 1943-1946 (Box 108, Folder 6)
      July 1943-46.
    - Red Caps, 1942-1943 (Box 108, Folder 7)
      1942-June 1943.
    - Red Caps, 1933-1941 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - 230-462(c). Red Caps, Southern Pacific Railway (Pacific System) and Los Angeles Union Passenger Terminal, 1940-1945 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - 230-462(d). Red Caps-Florida, East Coast, 1941-1946 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Red Caps, Pennsylvania Railroad, 1940-1941 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - 230-462(E). Red Caps, Washington Terminal Company, 1941-1944 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Red Caps, "Bags and Baggage", 1941 (Box 108, Folder 13)
      April 1941-Oct. 1941.
    - 230-463(2a). Steamship Clerks, North Atlantic, 1933-1946 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - 230-463(3). Steamship Clerks, South Atlantic, 1933-1946 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - 230-463(4). Steamship Lines, Gulf Ports, 1933-1946 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-464. Organization
    - Dominion of Canada, 1930-1945 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Dominion of Canada, 1921-1929 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-465. Organization
    - Pullman Company, 1953-1955 (Box 109, Folder 7)
      July 1953-55.
    - Pullman Company, 1950-1953 (Box 109, Folder 8)
      July 1950-June 30, 1953.
    - Pullman Company, 1950 (Box 109, Folder 9)
      March 25, 1950-June 1950.
    - Pullman Company, 1949-1950 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Pullman Company, 1949-1950 (Box 109, Folder 11)
      Jan. 1949-March 24, 1950.
    - Pullman Company, 1948 (Box 109, Folder 12)
      Oct. 1948-Dec. 1948.
    - Pullman Company, 1948 (Box 109, Folder 13)
      Feb. 1948-Sept. 1948.
    - Pullman Company, 1947-1948 (Box 109, Folder 14)
      July 1947-Jan. 1948.
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1947 (Box 109, Folder 15)
      Sept. 1946-June 1947.
    - Pullman Company, General, 1946 (Box 110, Folder 1)
      Jan. 1946-Aug. 1946.
    - Pullman Company, 1934-1945 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Pullman Company, 1933 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Pullman Company, "The Pullman News", 1949 (Box 110, Folder 4)
      Jan. 1949.
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Pullman Company, 1946-1949 (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-466. Organization
    - Salt Lake & Utah Railroad Corporation, 1933-1946 (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-467. Organization
    - Utah-Idaho Central Railroad, 1936-1947 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-468. Organization
    - Grain Elevators, Canada, 1937-1947 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Grain Elevators, Canada, 1936 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-469. Organization
    - Western Passenger Association (Scott Ticket Agency), 1937-1943 (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-471. Organization
    - Merchants Despatch Transportation Corporation, 1937-1955 (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-472. Organization
    - East Broad Top Railroad & Coal Company, 1939-1955 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 230-473. Organization
    - Fort Worth Stock Yards Company, 1940-1944 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 230-474. Organization. City.
    - 230-474-1. Birmingham, Alabama, 1945 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - 230-474-2. Buffalo, New York, 1933-1943 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - 230-474-3. Columbus, Ohio, 1923-1944 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - 230-474-5. Dayton, Ohio, 1941-1945 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - 230-474-5. Dayton, Ohio, 1923-1929 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - 230-474-6. Denver, Colorado, 1933-1947 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - 230-474-6. Denver, Colorado, 1934 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - 230-474-7. Memphis, Tennessee, 1927-1951 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - 230-474-7. Memphis, Tennessee, 1924 (Box 110, Folder 27)
    - 230-474-8. New York City, 1933-1944 (Box 110, Folder 28)
    - 230-474-8. New York City, 1922-1930 (Box 110, Folder 29)
    - 230-474-4. Dallas, Texas, 1926-1950 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - 230-474-9. San Francisco, California, 1933-1945 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - 230-474-9. San Francisco, California, 1925 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - 230-474-10. Salt Lake City, Utah, 1925-1948 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - 230-474-11. Chicago, Illinois, 1940-1948 (Box 111, Folder 5)
      Nov. 1940-48.
    - 230-474-11. Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1940 (Box 111, Folder 6)
      1921-Oct. 1940.
    - 230-474-13. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1921-1934 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - 230-474-14. Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1921-1942 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - 230-474-15. Fort Wayne, Indiana, 1922-1924 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - 230-474-16. Great Falls, Montana, 1923-1928 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - 230-474-17. Mobile, Alabama, 1923 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - 230-474-18. St. Louis, Missouri, 1932-1947 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - 230-474-18. St. Louis, Missouri, 1921-1929 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - 230-474-19. Boston, Massachusetts, 1925-1938 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - 230-474-20. Cleveland, Ohio, 1932-1937 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - 230-474-20. Cleveland, Ohio, 1923-1931 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - 230-474-21. Raleigh, North Carolina, 1929 (Box 111, Folder 17)
      1929 July
    - 230-474-22. Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1924-1934 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - 230-474-23. Iola, Kansas, 1924 (Box 111, Folder 19)
      Feb. 1924.
    - 230-474-24. Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1924-1949 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - 230-474-25. South Bend, Indiana, 1927 (Box 111, Folder 21)
      1927 March
    - 230-474-26. Pontiac, Michigan, 1928 (Box 111, Folder 22)
      1928 June
    - 230-474-27. Baltimore, Maryland, 1921-1927 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - 230-474-28. Omaha, Nebraska, 1922-1929 (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - 230-474-29. Louisville, Kentucky, 1924-1937 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - 230-474-30. Evansville, Indiana, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 26)
      1926 April
    - 230-474-31. Green Bay, Wisconsin, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 27)
      Feb. 1926-April 1926.
    - 230-474-32. Kansas City, Missouri, 1926-1933 (Box 111, Folder 28)
    - 230-474-33. Erie, Pennsylvania, 1925-1933 (Box 111, Folder 29)
    - 230-474-34. Toledo, Ohio, 1925-1935 (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - 230-474-35. Buffalo, New York, 1925-1930 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - 230-474-36. Springfield, Missouri, 1925 (Box 111, Folder 32)
      1925 July
    - 230-474-37. Jamesville, Wisconsin, 1925-1929 (Box 111, Folder 33)
    - 230-474-38. Wichita, Kansas, 1925-1933 (Box 111, Folder 34)
    - 230-474-39. Lima, Ohio, 1922-1929 (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - 230-474-40. Kankakee, Illinois, 1926-1934 (Box 111, Folder 36)
    - 230-474-42. Moberly, Missouri, 1924 (Box 111, Folder 37)
      Sept. 1924-Oct. 1924.
    - 230-474-43. Princeton, Indiana, 1924 (Box 111, Folder 38)
      Oct. 1, 1924.
    - 230-474-44. Des Moines, Iowa, 1924-1925 (Box 111, Folder 39)
    - 230-474-45. Richmond, Virginia, 1927-1928 (Box 111, Folder 40)
    - 230-474-46. Indianapolis, Indiana, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 41)
    - 230-474-46. Indianapolis, Indiana, 1922-1942 (Box 111, Folder 42)
    - 230-474-47. Los Angeles, California, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 43)
    - 230-474-47. Los Angeles, California, 1921-1930 (Box 111, Folder 44)
    - 230-474-48. Portland, Oregon, 1924-1926 (Box 111, Folder 45)
    - 230-474-49. Russelville, Kentucky, 1922 (Box 111, Folder 46)
    - 230-474-50. Poplar Bluff, Missouri, 1921 (Box 111, Folder 47)
    - 230-474-51. East St. Louis, Illinois, 1923-1934 (Box 111, Folder 48)
    - 230-474-41. Atlanta, Georgia, 1925-1950 (Box 111, Folder 49)
    - 230-474-52. Seattle, Washington, 1924 (Box 111, Folder 50)
      Feb. 1924-March 1924.
    - 230-474-53. Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1925 (Box 111, Folder 51)
    - 230-474-54. Portsmouth, Virginia, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 52)
      March 1926-April 1926.
  - Sub-Series 230-475. Organization
    - American Airlines, Inc., 1956-1965 (Box 111, Folder 53)
      Jan. 1, 1956-May 31, 1965.
    - American Airlines, Inc., 1944-1955 (Box 111, Folder 54)
      1944-Dec. 31, 1955.
    - American Airlines, Questionnaire, 1956 (Box 111, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 230-476. Organization
    - Kansas City Connecting Railroad Company, 1940-1944 (Box 111, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 230-477. Organization
    - Macon, Dublin & Savannah, 1945-1946 (Box 111, Folder 57)
    - Macon, Dublin & Savannah, 1935-1942 (Box 111, Folder 58)
    - Macon, Dublin & Savannah Railway Company, 1947 (Box 111, Folder 59)
      Jan. 1947-April 1947.
  - Sub-Series 230-478. Organization
    - Columbia Terminals Company, 1934-1946 (Box 111, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 230-479. Organization
    - Birmingham Southern Railroad, 1937-1956 (Box 111, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 230-480. Organization
    - National Airlines, Inc., 1957 (Box 112, Folder 1)
      March 1, 1957-March 31, 1957.
    - National Airlines, Inc., 1957 (Box 112, Folder 2)
      Jan. 1957- Feb. 1957.
    - National Airlines, Inc., 1956 (Box 112, Folder 3)
      Nov. 1956-Dec. 1956.
    - National Airlines, Inc., 1956 (Box 112, Folder 4)
      Jan. 1956-Oct. 1956.
    - National Airlines, Inc., 1947-1955 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - National Airlines, Inc., 1946 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-482. Organization
    - Cumberland & Pennsylvania Railroad Company, 1946 (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-486. Organization
    - Waterloo, Cedar Falls & Northern, 1935-1954 (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-488. Organization
    - Western Air Lines, Inc., 1958-1960 (Box 112, Folder 9)
      1958-Dec. 12, 1960.
    - Western Air Lines, Inc., 1952-1957 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Western Air Lines, Inc., 1947-1951 (Box 112, Folder 11)
      July 1947-51.
    - Western Air Lines, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 112, Folder 12)
      1946-June 1947.
  - Sub-Series 230-489. Organization
    - Chicago & Southern Air Lines, 1947-1951 (Box 112, Folder 13)
      Nov. 1947-51.
    - Chicago & Southern Air Lines, 1946-1947 (Box 112, Folder 14)
      1946-Oct. 1947.
  - Sub-Series 230-490. Organization
    - Mid-Continent Airlines, 1946-1947 (Box 112, Folder 15)
      1946-Feb 1947.
    - Mid-Continent Airlines, 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 1)
      Feb. 1952-53.
    - Mid-Continent Airlines, 1948-1952 (Box 113, Folder 2)
      1948-Jan. 1952.
    - Mid-Continent Airlines, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-491. Organization
    - Greyhound Bus Depot of Atlanta, Georgia, Inc., 1946-1952 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-492. Organization
    - Salt Lake Union Stock Yards Company, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-493. Organization
    - American Bus Lines, Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-494. Organization
    - Taca Airways Agency, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-495. Organization
    - Delta Air Lines, 1949-1956 (Box 113, Folder 9)
      March 15, 1949-56.
    - Delta Air Lines, 1956 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Delta Air Lines, 1946-1949 (Box 113, Folder 11)
      1946-March 14, 1949.
  - Sub-Series 230-496. Organization
    - Toronto, Hamilton & Buffalo Railway, 1942-1946 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-497. Organization
    - Peoria Union Bus Depot, 1945-1947 (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-498. Organization
    - East Tennessee & Western North Carolina, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-499. Organization
    - Bamberger Railroad Company, 1946-1959 (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-500. Organization
    - Bingham & Garfield Railway, Nevada Northern Railway, 1941-1948 (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-501. Organization
    - Jersey City Stock Yards, Inc., 1946-1952 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-504. Organization
    - Trailways Union Bus Depot, Kansas City, Missouri, 1946-1947 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 230-505. Organization
    - Louisiana & Northwest Railroad, 1930-1949 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 230-507. Organization
    - Mississippi Central Railroad Company, 1941-1946 (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-508. Organization
    - Tooele Valley Railroad, 1946-1952 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-509. Organization
    - Atlantic Greyhound Lines, 1946 (Box 113, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-510. Organization
    - American Overseas Airlines, 1946-1949 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 230-513. Organization
    - Missouri Pacific Transportation Company Bus Depot-Memphis, Tennessee, 1947-1949 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 230-514. Organization
    - Fort Smith Bus Terminal, 1946-1947 (Box 113, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 230-516. Organization
    - Continental Air Lines, Inc., 1946-1955 (Box 113, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 230-517. Organization
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1959-1964 (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 113, Folder 27)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1952-1956 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1949-1951 (Box 114, Folder 1)
      April 1949-51.
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1948-1949 (Box 114, Folder 2)
      May 1948-March 1949.
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1947-1948 (Box 114, Folder 3)
      August 1947-April 1948.
    - Braniff Airways, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 114, Folder 4)
      1946-July 1947.
  - Sub-Series 230-518. Organization
    - Inland Airlines, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-520. Organization
    - Empire Air Lines, Inc., New York, 1946 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-521. Organization
    - Carolina Coach Company, 1946-1947 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-525. Organization
    - Eastern Canada, 1921-1932 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-526. Organization
    - Keokuk Union Depot, 1930-1942 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-527. Organization
    - Goodrich Lines Steamship Company, 1930 (Box 114, Folder 10)
      Jan. 1930.
  - Sub-Series 230-528. Organization
    - Westchester and Boston Railroad, 1930-1931 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-529. Organization
    - Onward Lodge No. 154-Trenton, New Jersey, 1921 (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-530. Organization
    - Radio Operators, 1929 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-531. Organization
    - Tractor Drivers, 1928-1929 (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-532. Organization
    - Street Car Employees, 1929 (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-533. Organization
    - Republic of Mexico, 1930-1931 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Republic of Mexico, 1921-1932 (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 230-536. Organization
    - McCloud River Railroad, 1934 (Box 114, Folder 18)
      Sept. 1934.
  - Sub-Series 230-537. Organization
    - Manufacturers Junction Railway, 1934-1949 (Box 114, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-538. Organization
    - Northern Transportation Company, 1934-1936 (Box 114, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-539. Organization
    - Independent Subway System of New York City, 1934 (Box 114, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-540. Organization
    - Puget Sound Navigation Company, 1934 (Box 114, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 230-541. Organization
    - Indiana Railroad, 1934-1940 (Box 114, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 230-542. Organization
    - Railroad Refrigeration Companies, 1934-1935 (Box 114, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 230-543. Organization
    - Illinois Power and Light Company, 1934-1937 (Box 114, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 230-544. Organization
    - Chicago, Springfield & St. Louis Railway Company, Jacksonville & Havana Railroad Company, 1933-1937 (Box 114, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 230-546. Organization
    - Southern Pacific, Golden Gate Ferries, 1933-1936 (Box 114, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 230-547. Organization
    - Consolidated Fruit Company, 1933 (Box 114, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 230-548. Organization
    - Barge Lines, 1933-1942 (Box 114, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 230-549. Organization
    - Mississippi Export Railroad, 1939-1953 (Box 114, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 230-550. Organization
    - Midland Continental Railway, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 230-551. Organization
    - Copper River & Northwestern Railway Company, 1938 (Box 114, Folder 32)